learnhowtobecome.org 2019-11-04

# Privacy Policy | LearnHowToBecome.org

Privacy Policy 

## **Our Privacy Policy**

Since we launched in early 2014, our website visitors and community partners have trusted LearnHowtoBecome.org with providing high quality information and data for prospective students, teachers, schools and universities, as well as career centers, with keeping their personal information private. 

## **We Protect Your Information**

Our terms of use and privacy policy extends online to our website, and our primary focus is providing free information and web tools for students and non-profits across the globe. When a website chooses to use our tools and resources they are doing so without financial charge, and without providing personal information.

In an effort to remain transparent, here our more details on our data policies. LearnHowToBecome.org does collect two kinds of information from those who use our site: _submitted information_ and _automatic information_.

_AUTOMATIC INFORMATION_ is anonymous information that is automatically cataloged as you interact with our site. Examples of this type of data includes, but is not limited to, your browser version, operating system version, and your computer's IP address. This data helps us improve user experience, such as creating more compatable pages or more relevant, tailored content. We use “cookies” to collect this anonymous data for analytics, site optimization and customized advertising and marketing campaigns. 

As a user of LearnHowToBecome.org, you acknowledge and agree that this automatic data may be shared with schools, affiliated companies, and third parties for the purpose of providing information about degrees, programs and other education-related products and services.

_SUBMITTED INFORMATION_ includes any data that is voluntarily supplied and submitted by users through various web forms. Examples of this data may include any personal contact information you provide, such as your name, telephone number, mailing address or email address. We may collect, store and share this submitted information with schools and other third parties to provide users with information about the schools themselves, their programs, and additional education-related services.

By submitting this information, you authorize LearnHowToBecome.org and our affiliated schools and partners to contact you, in accordance with all applicable laws. Contact may be by phone, through text messages, or by email or mail regarding education and related topics. Submission also marks acknowledgement and agreement that we may retain the right to release collected information, including your personally identifiable information, as needed, to businesses providing our company with administration services, such email delivery. Additionally, your action grants us, our affiliates, and our partners and vendors the right to contact you for a period of time, and relinquish any rights granted to you by the Do Not Call list or other applicable law. Your submission serves as an omission to Do Not Call requirements established by state and federal governments and may exempt us from other applicable laws.

Any communication you may receive any email from us, a school, or third party, will also provide the ability to unsubscribe through a link in the email. If you choose to unsubscribe, you will be removed from further mailings from that sender.

In circumstances required by law, we also retain the right to release your personal information. This may include such instances as to abide by a subpoena or other legal preceeding. This will be when, in good faith, we believe it is necessary to preserve our rights, ensure the safety of you or others, explore alleged fraud, to reply to a government or legal request, and/or in the instance that LearnHowToBecome.org is merging, acquisitioning, or selling some or all of its assets to a third party.

In addition, we recommend that you revisit this document periodically to stay up-to-date with our practices concerning your privacy and other important information. We reserve the right to revise our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy if changes in our practice our made.

## More About Our Use of Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of data sent from a website and stored in the user’s web browser, including for technical purposes such as web analytics. By using this website, you acknowledge that we use cookies and consent to our use of cookies. Our web analytics are primarily performed using Google Analytics, a tool provided by Google, Inc.

Advertising cookies do not contain personally identifiable information and allow users to remain anonymous. However, they do permit advertisers to make ads more relevant to the user’s interests. Advertising cookies are sometimes referred to as third-party cookies because they track navigation and publish ads on behalf of third parties. For more information about Google Analytics and its uses, check Google’s privacy policy at <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245>.

LearnHowToBecome.org, including services and partnerships with vendors and third-party service providers, may use cookies for Web analytics such as demographic and other anonymous data for web optimization and other analysis, and “lead auditing” to ensure the accuracy, relevance and validity of submitted information. In addition, our use of marketing and conversion-tracking cookies is for, but not limited to, targeting and optimizing digital ad serving to improve relevance, user experience, and advertising effectiveness.

You can remove cookies through your browser settings at any time, though you may need to do this on a per use and not one-time basis. You can also generally opt-out of receiving personalized ads from third party advertisers and ad networks who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or who follow the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising by visiting the opt-out pages on the NAI website and DAA website.

## **Emailing Learn How to Become**

If you would like to contact us, please email us at [contact@learnhowtobecome.org.](mailto:contact@learnhowtobecome.org) We may retain your email message, our reply and your email address as part of our ongoing customer service initiatives. We reserve the right to contact you after you have contacted us. We may send future email and/or surveys to you about LearnHowtoBecome.org. You always have the right to notify us via email if you wish to discontinue electronic communication, and we will promptly adhere to your request by removing you from our email contact list.

You can find out more about theLearnHowtoBecome.org team here: /about-us/. Terms of use and privacy policy last updated January 5, 2019.  
Thank you for using [LearnHowtoBecome.org](https://www.learnhowtobecome.org/), we hope you visit again soon.
